http://www.1stwindows.com/legal.htm

SIGN IN 0DELIVERY TO:unknownToggle navigation Shop MilgardJeld-WenVeluxNovagardPlyGem
Windows
Doors
Skylights
Accessories
Comparison PricingInformation Learning CenterHow ToFAQHelpContactProfessional Services Professional InstallationContractor ProgramContractor ApplicationMy Account View AccountSave CartGenerate QuoteCheck Out Sales and Service Agreement Terms and Conditions of SaleAll sales are final. Your credit card will be processed at the time of the order."ARBITRATION OF DISPUTESAny controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this contract or breach thereof shall be settled by arbitration in accordance with the Uniform Rules for Better Business Bureau Arbitration, and the judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitrator's may be entered in any court having Jurisdiction thereof."Return Policy:  All windows and doors are made to order items that are non-returnable or refundable. They are custom made to your specifications for your project. Always check the order upon delivery carefully to make sure they match what you ordered. The manufacturers tolerance for measurements is + or - 1/8th inch. It is the buyers responsibility to make sure that your windows/doors will meet all your state and local building codes.Shipping: A set shipping fee will apply per manufacture for all orders (except for Velux orders where shipping is free regardless of size or number of skylights ordered). See Shipping Page for Manufacturer Shipping Rates. Orders are typically fulfilled and delivered within 12-16 working days.  All agreements contingent upon strikes, accidents or delays beyond our control.Tax: All purchases within California will be subject to a sales tax of 8.25%.  For all purchases outside of California, the contractor is required to pay all local and state taxes.Accurate Information: As further consideration for the 1stwindows.com membership, you agree to: (1) provide certain current, complete and accurate information about you as required by the application process; and (2) maintain and update this information as needed to keep it current, complete and accurate. We rely on this information to send you important information and notices regarding your account and our services.Our Privacy Statement: After you've signed up for our services, we may be in communication with you about your account, new passwords, Items on sale, technical questions you may have about services provided by us, or any other matter relating to those services. Those communications are essential to our relationship with you and to our ability to provide you with quality services that are responsive to your needs. At the same time, those communications give us helpful insights about you, your preferencesand the ways in which we might improve our services. We therefore may maintain this information for future use.The information we receive from or about you is stored on systems designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of that information. We also encrypt your transmission of sensitive information to us (e.g., credit card numbers, account passwords) in the interest of heightened privacy protection and information integrity.You have the ability to correct or change certain information in our records, such asyour address and contact information. You may change this information at any timeand as often as necessary. If you need assistance or have questions about correcting information, you can contact us via e-mail.Another example of our use of information to enhance the experience of users in our network of sites is our reliance on cookie files. We use cookie files to make it easier for users to access our site or services. A cookie file is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You may refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser; however, some of our sites may require a cookie for access.You agree that we, in our sole discretion, may modify our privacy statement. You agree that, by using our services after modifications to the privacy statement become effective, you have agreed to these modifications. We will not process the personal data that we collect from you in a way incompatible with the purposes and other limitations described in our privacy statement and we will take reasonable precautions to protect your personal data from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.RecentMilgard Lead Time as of 8/16/2017Milgard Window Lead Time as of 7/28/2017Milgard Window Lead Time as of 7/26/17 E-Business CenterContractorArchitectManufacturerInformationMilgard Service RequestTerm of serviceReturn PolicyOur GuaranteeLinks1stPricing.com Reference #About UsSite MapCopyright © 1stwindows.com 2000-2020. all rights reserved.
